- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_01_Welcome
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_01_Welcome_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_01_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_01_Welcome_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_01_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_01_Welcome_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_01_Welcome_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_01_Welcome_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_01_Welcome_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_01_Welcome_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_01_Welcome_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_02_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_01_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_02_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_02_Maudlinbugs_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_03_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_02_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_03_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_03_CatchSturgeon_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_04_Carpenter
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_04_Carpenter_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_04_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_03_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_04_Carpenter_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_04_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_04_Carpenter_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_04_Carpenter_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_04_Carpenter_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_04_Carpenter_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_04_Carpenter_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_04_Carpenter_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_05_Florist
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_05_Florist_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_05_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_04_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_05_Florist_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_05_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_05_Florist_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_05_Florist_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_05_Florist_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_05_Florist_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_05_Florist_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_05_Florist_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_06_Beekeep
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_06_Beekeep_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_06_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_05_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_06_Beekeep_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_06_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_06_Beekeep_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_06_Beekeep_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_06_Beekeep_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_06_Beekeep_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_06_Beekeep_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_06_Beekeep_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_07_Baker
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_07_Baker_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_07_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_06_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_07_Baker_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_07_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_07_Baker_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_07_Baker_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_07_Baker_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_07_Baker_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_07_Baker_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_07_Baker_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_08_Poet
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_08_Poet_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_08_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_07_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_08_Poet_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_08_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_08_Poet_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_08_Poet_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_08_Poet_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_08_Poet_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_08_Poet_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_08_Poet_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
- ObjectiveID: 13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand
  Type: Event
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_container
  NpcDestinationId: 1338_MasterOfCeremonies
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 13_Summer_09_2023
  RequiredAchievementId: 13_Summer_08_2023
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 13_Summer_09_QuestReward
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: false
  CanBeAbandoned: ""
  Title: "@13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_objective_title"
  Description: "@13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@13_Summer_09_PlayWithBand_complete_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  ScheduleId: EventSummer
  HideAvailableMapIcon: true
